<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ProbQuest</string>

    <string name="title_study">Study</string>
    <string name="title_tests">Tests</string>
    <string name="title_games">Games</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation">NavigationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="roll_dice_mechanics">
        1. Players begin by predicting whether the sum of two rolled dice will be less than 7, greater than 7, or equal to 7.\n
        \n2. Once the prediction is made, click the roll button to initiate the dice roll, and the resulting numbers are added up to determine the sum.\n
        \n3. If the player\'s prediction matches the actual sum, they win the round and earn points. However, an incorrect prediction results in a point deduction for the player.
    </string>

    <string name="high_low_mechanics">
        1. The game begins by automatically revealing the first card from a deck of eight cards.\n
        \n2. The player then predicts whether the next card will be higher or lower in value compared to the last card.\n
        \n3. If the prediction is correct, the player wins the round and earns points. However, if the prediction is incorrect, the players loses points.\n
        \n4. The game continues in rounds until all eight cards are revealed.
    </string>

    <string name="color_roulette_mechanics">
        1. There\'s a roulette wheel with 16 slots, each colored red, blue, green, or yellow. The number of slots for each color is different.\n
        \n2. The player chooses one of the four options, each representing colored red, blue, green, or yellow.\n
        \n3. The player then spins the wheel, and if it lands on one of the specified colors from their chosen option, they win the round and earn points.
    </string>

    <string-array name="topic_titles">
        <item>Simple Events</item>
        <item>Compound Events</item>
        <item>Mutually Exclusive Events</item>
        <item>Independent Events</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="direction">
        Read and understand each question carefully and select your answer from the multiple-choice options.\n
        \nChoose only one answer per question and click next to proceed to the next item.\n
        \nYou have a 60 seconds time limit per question.\n
        \nYour score will display after answering all 10 questions. Good luck!
    </string>


</resources>