<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ProbQuest</string>

    <string name="title_study">Study</string>
    <string name="title_tests">Tests</string>
    <string name="title_games">Games</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation">NavigationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="roll_dice_mechanics">
        1. Players begin by predicting whether the sum of two rolled dice will be less than 7, greater than 7, or equal to 7.\n
        \n2. Once the prediction is made, click the roll button to initiate the dice roll, and the resulting numbers are added up to determine the sum.\n
        \n3. If the player\'s prediction matches the actual sum, they win the round and earn points. However, an incorrect prediction results in a point deduction for the player.
    </string>

    <string name="high_low_mechanics">
        1. The game begins by automatically revealing the first card from a deck of eight cards.\n
        \n2. The player then predicts whether the next card will be higher or lower in value compared to the last card.\n
        \n3. If the prediction is correct, the player wins the round and earns points. However, if the prediction is incorrect, the players loses points.\n
        \n4. The game continues in rounds until all eight cards are revealed.
    </string>

    <string name="color_roulette_mechanics">
        1. The roulette wheel consists of 16 slots, each colored as red, blue, green, or yellow. The distribution of colors across the wheel is uneven.\n
        \n2. The player makes a prediction by choosing one of the four options: red, blue, green, or yellow.\n
        \n3. Upon spinning the wheel, if it lands on the color predicted by the player, they win the round and earn points. Conversely, if the outcome differs from their prediction, points are deducted.
    </string>

    <string name="puzzle_mechanics">
        1. Each level(easy, medium, hard) consists of 10 probability puzzles.\n
        \n2. Players have 1 minute and 30 seconds (1:30) to write and submit their answer for each puzzle.\n
        \n3. Upon submission, the system immediately evaluates the answer for correctness. Correct answers earn points, while incorrect answers result in no points awarded.\n
        \n4. If the player fails to submit their answer within the time limit or provides an incorrect response, they are given the option to retry the puzzle.\n
        \n5. After completing all 10 puzzles in a level, the player\'s total score is calculated and displayed. Players have the option to retry the game.
    </string>

    <string-array name="topic_titles">
        <item>Simple Events</item>
        <item>Compound Events</item>
        <item>Mutually Exclusive Events</item>
        <item>Independent Events</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="direction">
        Read and understand each question carefully and select your answer from the multiple-choice options.\n
        \nChoose only one answer per question and click next to proceed to the next item.\n
        \nYou have a 1 minute ans 30 seconds time limit per question.\n
        \nYour score will display after answering all 10 questions. Good luck!
    </string>


</resources>